

SANTIYA GEORGIEVA

Front-End Developer

ABOUT ME

Extremely motivated to constantly develop new skills, both soft and technical, and grow professionally. Passioned person with interests incutting edge technologies. Possessing a broader perspective as a Front-end developer based on my current experience and achieved with self-study, perseverance and ambition. Active involvement in the open source community. Keep touch with the latest trends on Reddit, Medium, and so on.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

Front-end	Developer Tools	Version Control	Project Management tools
 ReactJS 	 VS Code 	Git	
 Redux 	Atom	 Github 	 Redmine
 Angular 2+ 	 IntelliJ based IDEs 	 Gitlab 	 Assembla
• ES2015/2016	 Sublime Text 3 	 Bitbucket 	Jira

Brackets

Design Tools

Material-Ul

iQuery

- Adobe XD
- Zeplin for Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop

Twitter Bootstrap

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

myPos AD Technologies 03.2021 - 06.2022

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Prime Holding Jsc. 06.2019 - 02.2021

INTERN FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Prime Holding Jsc. 10.2018 to 06.2019

INTERSHIP TRAINEE AS FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Prime Holding Jsc. 07.2018 to 09.2018

STUDENT TRAINEE AS FRONT-END DEVELOPER

OneCreative Media 07.2017 to 08.2017 and 07.2016 to 08.2016

GET IN TOUCH WITH ME

Varna, Bulgaria +359 883 45 40 41 santiyageorgieva@yahoo.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/santiyageorgieva-b97916147

PROJECTS

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: React, Redux, SCSS Duration: 6 months

- Creating reuseble components
- Fixing major issues regard product specifications
- Refactoring components and styles based on new design changes
- Create new urgent components without design templates
- Make proposition of design changes for better user experience, readability
- · Add new React libraries to achieve product specification

EDUCATION

2018 BSc(Hons) in ComputerSystems Technology "Angel Kanchev" University, Ruse

2014

High School "Jordan Yovkov" Tutrakan, Silistra Province

SOFT SKILLS

- Strong work ethic
- Empathic listener and persuasive speaker
- Kind and helpful to others
- Enjoy working as a team members well as independently
- · Attention to details
- Fluent english (B2)

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: React, Redux, SCSS

Duration: 10 months

- Creating reuseble components
- Fixing major issues regard product specifications
- · Refactoring components and styles based on new design changes
- Create new urgent components without design templates
- · Make proposition of design changes for better user experience, readability
- · Add new React libraries to achieve product specification

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: React, Redux, SCSS

Duration: 8 months

- · Creating reuseble components
- Fixing major issues regard product specifications
- · Refactoring components and styles based on new design changes
- · Create new urgent components without design templates
- · Make proposition of design changes for better user experience, readability

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: ¡Query, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS

Duration: 1 month

• Fixing major issues regard specifications

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: Angular 8+, Telerik DevCraft/Kendo UI, SCSS, DevOps (Docker,Docker Compose)

Duration: 9 months

- Making a huge reskin (refactoring code) of a major fuctionallity
- · Assisting to the team when creating the mobile version of the system
- Being a part of a sustaining (cross-functional) team for fixing major bugs, regressions etc. and handling high priority tasks in production
- · Making propositions for better implementation of functionalities to the clients, if
- needed. Helping to the teammates with their tasks or problems related to the project configurations
- Being a part of large front-end team

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS

Duration: 2 months

 Assisting of the front-end team to make a reskin (refactoring code) of the system regard the styles and functionality

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: Wordpress

Duration: 1 month

- Creating a few templates using the embedded plugin (already installed and used) from the client for the website of the company
- · Fixing issues regarding the styles
- Making a tutorial/guideline for the clients to change the content of the website afterthe described above changes

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: React, Redux, JavaScript, CSS Transitions, SCSS

Duration: 3 months

- Assisting with the front-end development for the reskin of the system
- Developing own components (not using predefined from Bootstrap/Material Design)
- · Refactoring the business logic of the components to follow the best practices
- · Creating Javascript and CSS Transitions

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: React, Redux, JavaScript, Material UI, SCSS

Duration: 7 months

- · Fixing a major bugs in production mode
- · Integrating REST API Services
- · Improving the responsive design of the app
- Using Material UI for React
- Finding BE gaps
- Helping managing the tasks for the team

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: Angular 6, Angular Admin Template \cdot CoreUI for Angular Duration: 2 months

- Using reusable components
- · Using the Admin template for Angular
- Integrating REST API Services
- · Improving the security of the FE part
- · Finding BE gaps

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: Angular 6, HTML & Bootstrap Website Templates Colorlib Duration: 1 month

- Seperate the templates to pices, so they can be used as own independent
- · components Integrating REST API Services

CLIENT/COMPANY: UNDER NDA

Technologies used: Angular 6, HTML & Bootstrap Website Templates Colorlib Duration: 1 month

- Seperate the templates to pices, so they can be used as own independent
- · components Integrating REST API Services

CLIENT/COMPANY: VIG GROUP LTD.TRANSPORT & DISTRIBUTION COMPANY

Technologies used: Javascript, PHP Mailer, Twitter Bootstrap Duration: 2 months

- Creating a simple design of the project UI/UX.
- · Developing the responsive website
- · Using the PHP mailer for the contact form
- Integrating Google Maps API Services

PERSONAL PROJECTS

CLIENT/COMPANY: NONE (OPEN SOURCE)
PROJECT NAME: HEALTHY BENEFITS

Technologies used: React, Redux, Javascript, Twitter Bootstrap Duration: 8 months

- Reworking the front-end part to achieve a better performance app which follows thelatest cutting edge technologies
- · Developing dynamic components
- Learning new technologies in order to create, extend and improve the fuctionallity of existing project

CLIENT/COMPANY: NONE (OPEN SOURCE) PROJECT NAME: HEALTHY BENEFITS

Technologies used: Symphony, Twig, Twitter Bootstrap Duration: 2 months

- · Developing a high dynimicly web-based system with MVC architecture
- Inventing the UX/UI design to provides a modern web app for the end users
- Implementing the responsive design
- Writing an excellent documentation for the project

CLIENT/COMPANY: NONE (OPEN SOURCE) PROJECT NAME: HEALTHY BENEFITS

Technologies used: Javascript, Twitter Bootstrap

Duration: 3 months

Represents a web-based system of the electronic reference book of RU "AngelKanchev".
 The responsibilities within the project: front-end development and co-working with the rest of the team (UI designer, QA).

TRAINING

- · Diploma project
- Course project created during my university education
- English language Course, Upperintermidiate (B2) certificate from Info Bulgaria Educational Center